{"481322438.975125": {
"front": "481322486.504237",
"right": "null",
"back": "null",
"left": "null",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481322486.504237":{
"front":"481322624.018600",
"right":"null",
"back":"481322438.975125",
"left":"null",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481322624.018600":{
"front":"481322643.291428",
"right":"",
"back":"481322486.504237",
"left":"",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481322643.291428":{
"front":"481322666.755545",
"right":"",
"back":"481322624.018600",
"left":"",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481322666.755545":{
"front":"481322692.750440",
"right":"",
"back":"481322643.291428",
"left":"",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481322692.750440":{
"front":"",
"right":"",
"back":"481322666.755545",
"left":"481322711.293049",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481322711.293049":{
"front":"481322765.030766",
"right":"481322692.750440",
"back":"",
"left":"481322848.188596",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481322848.188596":{
"front":"481322799.065309",
"right":"481322711.293049",
"back":"481322889.852964",
"left":"481322937.972649",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481322765.030766":{
"front":"",
"right":"",
"back":"481322711.293049",
"left":"481322799.065309",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481322799.065309":{
"front":"",
"right":"481322765.030766",
"back":"481322848.188596",
"left":"",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481322889.852964":{
"front":"481322848.188596",
"right":"",
"back":"",
"left":"",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481322937.972649":{
"front":"481322983.244987",
"right":"481322848.188596",
"back":"",
"left":"481323086.140905",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481322983.244987":{
"front":"",
"right":"",
"back":"481322937.972649",
"left":"481323016.004880",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481323016.004880":{
"front":"",
"right":"481322983.244987",
"back":"",
"left":"481323037.484684",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481323037.484684":{
"front":"",
"right":"481323016.004880",
"back":"481323104.079978",
"left":"",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481323104.079978":{
"front":"481323037.484684",
"right":"481323086.140905",
"back":"",
"left":"481323158.832885",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481323086.140905":{
"front":"",
"right":"481322937.972649",
"back":"",
"left":"481323104.079978",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481323158.832885":{
"front":"481323191.204174",
"right":"481323104.079978",
"back":"",
"left":"481323227.626576",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481323191.204174":{
"front":"",
"right":"",
"back":"481323158.832885",
"left":"",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481323227.626576":{
"front":"",
"right":"481323158.832885",
"back":"",
"left":"481323261.027664",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481323261.027664":{
"front":"",
"right":"481323227.626576",
"back":"",
"left":"481323292.170249",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481323292.170249":{
"front":"",
"right":"481323261.027664",
"back":"481323325.720765",
"left":"481323363.930570",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481323363.930570":{
"front":"",
"right":"481323292.170249",
"back":"481323394.740455",
"left":"481323419.615934",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481323325.720765":{
"front":"481323292.170249",
"right":"",
"back":"",
"left":"",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481323394.740455":{
"front":"481323363.930570",
"right":"",
"back":"",
"left":"",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481323419.615934":{
"front":"481323478.210447",
"right":"481323363.930570",
"back":"",
"left":"481323553.473188",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481323478.210447":{
"front":"",
"right":"",
"back":"481323419.615934",
"left":"481323522.877238",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481323522.877238":{
"front":"",
"right":"481323478.210447",
"back":"481323553.473188",
"left":"",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481323553.473188":{
"front":"481323522.877238",
"right":"481323419.615934",
"back":"",
"left":"481323584.345160",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481323584.345160":{
"front":"481324006.031392",
"right":"481323553.473188",
"back":"",
"left":"481323610.439384",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481324006.031392":{
"front":"",
"right":"",
"back":"481323584.345160",
"left":"481323958.172695",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481323958.172695":{
"front":"",
"right":"481324006.031392",
"back":"",
"left":"481323919.620407",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481323919.620407":{
"front":"",
"right":"481323958.172695",
"back":"481323704.289111",
"left":"",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481323610.439384":{
"front":"",
"right":"481323584.345160",
"back":"",
"left":"481323682.181376",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481323682.181376":{
"front":"",
"right":"481323610.439384",
"back":"",
"left":"481323704.289111",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481323704.289111":{
"front":"481323919.620407",
"right":"481323682.181376",
"back":"",
"left":"481324098.571879",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481324098.571879":{
"front":"",
"right":"481323704.289111",
"back":"481324133.677319",
"left":"481324379.909598",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481324379.909598":{
"front":"",
"right":"481324098.571879",
"back":"",
"left":"",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481324133.677319":{
"front":"481324098.571879",
"right":"481324296.043075",
"back":"",
"left":"",
"rotate": "-180"
},
"481324296.043075":{
"front":"",
"right":"",
"back":"",
"left":"481324133.677319",
"rotate": "-180"
}
}
